Guide to the Harry Randall: Fifteenth International Brigade Films and Photographs ALBA.PHOTO.011
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series D: Miscellaneous, September 1937-June 1938; August 1938
  - Photo Unit #: D108 Fiesta in Quinto after Fuentes de Ebro [outdoors, crowd listening to a piano-player], 1937-10 (Box 8, Folder 11-1348)
    (Moscow Number: 5/181/5)
  - Photo Unit #: D110 English anti-tank battery at rest, Ambite, 1937-11 (Box 6, Folder 11-1796)
    (Moscow Number: 5/184/7)
  - Photo Unit #: D111 English anti-tank battery at rest, Ambite; [soldier playing a recorder], 1937-11 (Box 6, Folder 11-1800)
    (Moscow Number: 5/184/12)
  - Photo Unit #: D113 Major Modeste at 15th Brigade, Ambite, 1937-11 (Box 8, Folder 11-1349)
  - Photo Unit #: D114 Major Modesto at 15th Brigade at Ambite, 1937-11 (Box 3, Folder 11-1080)
    (Moscow Number: 5/175/7)
  - Photo Unit #: D115 Major Juan Modesto at 15th International Brigade at Ambite, 1937-11 (Box 6, Folder 11-1755)
    (Moscow Number: 5/175/6)
  - Photo Unit #: D116 Major Modesto at 15th Brigade at Ambite, 1937-11 (Box 3, Folder 11-1081)
    (Moscow Number: 5/175/8)
  - Photo Unit #: D117 Captain Hans Amlie (l.), Captain Malcolm Dunbar, Major Robert Merriman, Colonel Stephen Fuqua (American Military Attache ) in Quinto after Fuentes de Ebro, 1937-11 (Box 3, Folder 11-0842)
    (Moscow Number: 5/195/1)
  - Photo Unit #: D118 Colonel Stephen Fuqua, David Doran and Captain Hans Amlie at Fuentes de Ebro, 1937-11 (Box 8, Folder 11-1350)
  - Photo Unit #: D119 Colonel Stephen Fuqua (l.), David Doran and Captain Hans Amlie at Fuentes de Ebro, 1937-11 (Box 3, Folder 11-0843)
  - Photo Unit #: D120 Colonel Stephen Fuqua reviews troops at Quinto after Fuentes de Ebro, 1937-11 (Box 3, Folder 11-0844)
    (Moscow Number: 5/195/11)
  - Photo Unit #: D121 Colonel Stephen Fuqua reviews troops at Quinto after Fuentes de Ebro, 1937-11 (Box 3, Folder 11-0845)
  - Photo Unit #: D122 15th International Brigade in shower machine at Quinto after action at Fuentes de Ebro, 1937-10 (Box 6, Folder 11-1777)
    (Moscow Number: 5/181/3)
  - Photo Unit #: D123 Moving back to Quinto from Fuentes de Ebro Front, [soldiers in cart], 1937-10 (Box 6, Folder 11-1781)
    (Moscow Number: 5/181/10)
  - Photo Unit #: D124 Robert Minor at Fuentes action, 1937-11 (Box 3, Folder 11-0846)
  - Photo Unit #: D125 Robert Minor at Quinto during Fuentes de Ebro offensive, 1937-11 (Box 3, Folder 11-0847)
    (Moscow Number: 5/188/56)
  - Photo Unit #: D126 Lieutenant Colonel Vladimir Copic, Robert Minor and [?], 1937-11 (Box 3, Folder 11-0848)
    (Moscow Number: 5/177/14)
  - Photo Unit #: D127 Robert Minor in Quinto during Fuentes de Ebro, 1937-10 (Box 3, Folder 11-0849)
    (Moscow Number: 5/189/12)
  - Photo Unit #: D128 Robert Minor, Fuentes de Ebro, 1937-11 (Box 3, Folder 11-0850)
    (Moscow Number: 5/188/55)
  - Photo Unit #: D136 Students from Federation of University Students at 15th Brigade (Spanish Universal Federacion), 1937-11 (Box 3, Folder 11-1082)
  - Photo Unit #: D139 Scene at ceremony of presentation of flags to British Battalion, [with two flag bearers], 1937-12 (Box 6, Folder 11-1793)
    (Moscow Number: 5/184/4)
  - Photo Unit #: D148 General Walter examining a rifle, 1937-12 (Box 8, Folder 11-1351)
  - Photo Unit #: D149 Armored train in Quinto, 1937-10 (Box 3, Folder 11-0851)
  - Photo Unit #: D153 Jacques Lemare and Henri Cartier-Bresson filming at Quinto., 1937-10 (Box 1, Folder 11-0261)
  - Photo Unit #: D154 Henri Cartier-Bresson in Quinto (probably in October 1937), 1937-10 (Box 3, Folder 11-0852)
  - Photo Unit #: D160 Print from captured negative taken in Quinto action of Aug and Sep 1937, 1937-09 (Box 3, Folder 11-1196)
    (Moscow Number: 5/180/12)
  - Photo Unit #: D161 Meyer Levin of "Esquire" visits Lincoln-Washington Battalion at Alvares, 1937-12 (Box 3, Folder 11-0853)
  - Photo Unit #: D162 Ernest Hemingway with other American visitors to 15th International Brigade, 1937-12 (Box 8, Folder 11-1352)
  - Photo Unit #: D164 Ernest Hemingway, 1937-12 (Box 8, Folder 11-1353)
  - Photo Unit #: D165 Ernest Hemingway with other American visitors to 15th International Brigade, 1937-12 (Box 8, Folder 11-1354)
  - Photo Unit #: D166 [Men] of anti-tank [company?] reading [newspapers] from home [copy negative; transferred from the Victor Berch Papers, ALBA 080], 1937-12 (Box 6, Folder 11-1892)
  - Photo Unit #: D169 On the firing range, 1937-12 (Box 6, Folder 11-1801)
    (Moscow Number: 5/184/13)
  - Photo Unit #: D170 Rifle range, Mondejar [men lying on ground, taking aim], 1937-12 (Box 8, Folder 11-1355)
  - Photo Unit #: D184 David Doran at 24th Battalion, Taranca, 1937-12 (Box 3, Folder 11-1197)
  - Photo Unit #: D188 Brigade and English Battalion officers with William Rust and Harry Pollitt [not visible] at English Battalion [crowd of troops listening], 1937-12 (Box 8, Folder 11-1356)
  - Photo Unit #: D189 Harry Pollitt at English Battalion [copy negative; transferred from the Victor Berch Papers, ALBA 080], 1937-12 (Box 6, Folder 11-1893)
  - Photo Unit #: D192 Harry Pollitt [?] addressing English Battalion, 1938-09 (Box 6, Folder 11-1756)
    (Moscow Number: 5/176/2)
  - Photo Unit #: D193 Brigade and English Battalion officers William Rust and Harry Pollitt at English Battalion, 1937-12 (Box 8, Folder 11-1357)
  - Photo Unit #: D194 Brigade and English Battalion officers William Rust and Harry Pollitt at English Battalion [with group, arms raised in salute], 1937-12 (Box 8, Folder 11-1358)
  - Photo Unit #: D199 Washing clothes, 1937-12 (Box 3, Folder 11-1083)
  - Photo Unit #: D202 Train trip, Ambite, Alcaniz, 1937-12 (Box 3, Folder 11-1084)
  - Photo Unit #: D203 Anti-air Machine Gunner on Train, 1937-12 (Box 3, Folder 11-1085)
  - Photo Unit #: D204 On trip from Ambite to Alcaniz [group of men; railroad car with IB poster on it], 1937-12 (Box 8, Folder 11-1359)
  - Photo Unit #: D205 Anti-Aircraft Machine-Gunners on [roof of] train, 1937-12 (Box 8, Folder 11-1360)
  - Photo Unit #: D207 Trip from Ambite to Alcaniz, 1937-12 (Box 3, Folder 11-1086)
  - Photo Unit #: D214 On trip from Ambite to Alcaniz, 35th Division Artillery [2 men in open freight car], 1937-12 (Box 8, Folder 11-1361)
  - Photo Unit #: D215 Unloading, 1937-12 (Box 3, Folder 11-1087)
  - Photo Unit #: D217 15th International Brigade picking olives, Alcaniz, 1937-12 (Box 6, Folder 11-1762)
    (Moscow Number: 5/180/24)
  - Photo Unit #: D218 15th International Brigade men picking olives, Alcaniz, 1937-12 (Box 1, Folder 11-0262)
  - Photo Unit #: D221 Anti-Gas section of Lincoln-Washington, 1937-12 (Box 3, Folder 11-1088)
  - Photo Unit #: D222 Lieutenant Colonel Vladimir Copic addressing Lincoln-Washington and 24th Battalion Awards, Christmas, 1937-12 (Box 3, Folder 11-1089)
  - Photo Unit #: D224 Trip from Ambite to Alcaniz, 1937-12 (Box 3, Folder 11-0854)
  - Photo Unit #: D228 Morris Brier and Otto Reeves with Anti-war Machine-Gunner MacKenzie-Papineau Battalion, 1937-12 (Box 8, Folder 11-1362)
  - Photo Unit #: D229 Church, Masde las Matas where English and MacKenzie-Papineau were quartered, 1937-12 (Box 3, Folder 11-1090)
  - Photo Unit #: D231 General Walter [Karol Scwierczewski] examines a rifle in 15th Brigade, 1937-12 (Box 3, Folder 11-0855)
  - Photo Unit #: D232 Aragonese anarchist [Rufino Tio "Pipa"] in Alcorisa, 1937-12 (Box 3, Folder 11-1091)
  - Photo Unit #: D236 David Doran, Haldane, Robert Merriman, 1937-12 (Box 8, Folder 11-1363)
  - Photo Unit #: D237 Robert Merriman, [?] Haldane, Vladimir Copic, 1937-12 (Box 8, Folder 11-1364)
  - Photo Unit #: D239 An American of Lincoln-Washington Battalion, 1937-12 (Box 3, Folder 11-1092)
  - Photo Unit #: D240 Our trenches at Fuentes Caliente, 1938-01 (Box 3, Folder 11-1093)
  - Photo Unit #: D242 Lying down to get a drink, Fuentes Caliente, 1938-01 (Box 8, Folder 11-1365)
  - Photo Unit #: D244 [Soldier with machine gun] [copy negative; transferred from the Victor Berch Papers, ALBA 080], 1938-01 (Box 6, Folder 11-1894)
  - Photo Unit #: D245 Steaks, 1938-01 (Box 3, Folder 11-1094)
  - Photo Unit #: D248 Interior of a home near Teruel, 1938-01 (Box 3, Folder 11-1095)
  - Photo Unit #: D251 Sign outside Teruel, "Alto A Teruel", 1938-01 (Box 8, Folder 11-1366)
  - Photo Unit #: D252 Reading and rest room for men of our outfit, 1938-02 (Box 3, Folder 11-0856)
  - Photo Unit #: D258 MacKenzie-Papineau Battalion and civilian fiesta at Tivisa, [seated children], 1938-05 (Box 6, Folder 11-1839)
    (Moscow Number: 5/187/32)
  - Photo Unit #: D260 After Teruel [4 soldiers sitting against wall, one reading a newspaper], 1938-02 (Box 8, Folder 11-1367)
  - Photo Unit #: D261 After Teruel, 1938-02 (Box 3, Folder 11-0857)
  - Photo Unit #: D266 After Teruel, 1938-02 (Box 3, Folder 11-0858)
  - Photo Unit #: D267 After Teruel, 1938-02 (Box 3, Folder 11-0859)
  - Photo Unit #: D270 After Teruel, 1938-02 (Box 3, Folder 11-0860)
  - Photo Unit #: D271 After Teruel, 1938-02 (Box 3, Folder 11-0861)
  - Photo Unit #: D273 After Teruel, 1938-02 (Box 3, Folder 11-0862)
  - Photo Unit #: D274 After Teruel, 1938-02 (Box 3, Folder 11-0863)
  - Photo Unit #: D275 Ambulance, after Teruel, 1938-02 (Box 3, Folder 11-0864)
  - Photo Unit #: D278 Dental Wagon at work, "Doc" [Jack] Klein, 1938-02 (Box 3, Folder 11-0865)
  - Photo Unit #: D279 Ambulance, "From the Workers of West Virginia", 1938-02 (Box 8, Folder 11-1368)
  - Photo Unit #: D280 Ambulance labeled "The West Virginian No. 2"] and drivers [copy negative; transferred from the Victor Berch Papers, ALBA 080], 1938-02 (Box 6, Folder 11-1895)
  - Photo Unit #: D281 Kitchen [copy negative; transferred from the Victor Berch Papers, ALBA 080], 1938-02 (Box 6, Folder 11-1896)
  - Photo Unit #: D285 Recruits at Alcorisa, 1938-02 (Box 6, Folder 11-1369)
  - Photo Unit #: D289 Earl Browder addressing MacKenzie-Papineau at station near Teruel, 1938-02 (Box 3, Folder 11-1096)
  - Photo Unit #: D292 Print from captured negative, 1938-02 (Box 3, Folder 11-1097)
  - Photo Unit #: D295 Men of 59th Battalion who received awards at Christmas time, 1938-01 (Box 6, Folder 11-1826)
  - Photo Unit #: D296 Football game, 15th Brigade U.S. Alcorisa, Juventud Socialista Unificada, 1938-02 (Box 3, Folder 11-1098)
  - Photo Unit #: D300 Spectators at football game [including women], 1938-02 (Box 8, Folder 11-1370)
  - Photo Unit #: D303 Refugio near Lincoln-Washington Battalion kitchen, 1938-02 (Box 3, Folder 11-1099)
  - Photo Unit #: D304 Cedrilla, 1938-02 (Box 3, Folder 11-1100)
  - Photo Unit #: D305 Group of Spanish soldiers, on stone steps, 1938-02 (Box 8, Folder 11-1371)
  - Photo Unit #: D306 Festival, 15th International Brigade, Popular Front, 1938-02 (Box 3, Folder 11-0866)
  - Photo Unit #: D314 Shelters made by comrades of Company 2, 59th Battalion, 1938-03 (Box 3, Folder 11-1101)
  - Photo Unit #: D317 15th Brigade Estado Mayor [Headquarters] outside Hijar at retreat, 1938-03 (Box 3, Folder 11-1102)
  - Photo Unit #: D323 Meeting of Political Commissars of 15th Brigade with Luigi Gallo, 1938-03 (Box 3, Folder 11-1372)
    (Moscow Number: 5/189/22)
  - Photo Unit #: D324 Peasant weaving, 1938-03 (Box 3, Folder 11-1103)
  - Photo Unit #: D325 Outside Hijar, 1938-03 (Box 3, Folder 11-1104)
  - Photo Unit #: D326 Group, Genie of 61st Brigade waiting to go to front. Also point of road control. [group at checkpoint, some on ground with piles of gear], 1938-03 (Box 8, Folder 11-1373)
  - Photo Unit #: D329 Farmlands, Hijar, 1938-03 (Box 8, Folder 11-1374)
  - Photo Unit #: D331 Repairing clothing, MacKenzie-Papineau, 1938-03 (Box 3, Folder 11-1105)
  - Photo Unit #: D335 Women and children at Letur, 1938-03 (Box 8, Folder 11-1375)
  - Photo Unit #: D337 River Letux, 1938-03 (Box 3, Folder 11-1106)
  - Photo Unit #: D346 Water wheel, MacKenzie-Papineau Battalion, Ebro Front, 1938-05 (Box 3, Folder 11-0867)
  - Photo Unit #: D369 [Soldiers, group], 1938-01 (Box 3, Folder 11-1107)
  - Photo Unit #: D370 [Soldiers, group], 1938-01 (Box 3, Folder 11-1108)
  - Photo Unit #: D371 [Soldiers, talking], 1938-01 (Box 3, Folder 11-1109)
  - Photo Unit #: D372 [Three soldiers], 1938-01 (Box 3, Folder 11-1110)
  - Photo Unit #: D373 [Three soldiers], 1938-01 (Box 3, Folder 11-1111)
  - Photo Unit #: D377 [At the front], 1938-01 (Box 3, Folder 11-1112)
  - Photo Unit #: D380 [Officers addressing the troops (?)], 1938-01 (Box 3, Folder 11-1113)
  - Photo Unit #: D381 [Woman addressing the troops (?)], 1938-01 (Box 3, Folder 11-1114)
  - Photo Unit #: D387 [Soldiers, group], 1938-01 (Box 3, Folder 11-1115)
  - Photo Unit #: D390 [Soldiers in a bunker], 1938-01 (Box 3, Folder 11-1116)
  - Photo Unit #: D393 [Soldiers with auto], 1938-01 (Box 8, Folder 11-1376)
  - Photo Unit #: D394 [Soldiers with auto], 1938-01 (Box 8, Folder 11-1377)
  - Photo Unit #: D395 [3 soldiers, 3 women], 1938-01 (Box 8, Folder 11-1378)
  - Photo Unit #: D396 [Group of soldiers with one woman], 1938-01 (Box 8, Folder 11-1379)
  - Photo Unit #: D397 [Crowd, a few soldiers, mostly men and women civilians; car in background], 1938-01 (Box 8, Folder 11-1380)
  - Photo Unit #: D398 [Group of soldiers, same locale as D394, 395, 397], 1938-01 (Box 8, Folder 11-1381)
  - Photo Unit #: D399 [2 soldiers with bulletin board], 1938-05 (Box 8, Folder 11-1382)
  - Photo Unit #: D400 [3 soldiers], 1938-05 (Box 8, Folder 11-1383)
  - Photo Unit #: D401 International Brigade Conference, 1938-05 (Box 8, Folder 11-1384)
  - Photo Unit #: D402 [Officers addressing the troops], 1938-01 (Box 3, Folder 11-1117)
  - Photo Unit #: D403 [Officers addressing the troops], 1938-01 (Box 3, Folder 11-1118)
  - Photo Unit #: D405 [Soldiers, group], 1938-01 (Box 3, Folder 11-1119)
  - Photo Unit #: D409 [Officers addressing the troops], 1938-01 (Box 3, Folder 11-1120)
  - Photo Unit #: D410 International Brigade Conference, 1938-05 (Box 8, Folder 11-1385)
  - Photo Unit #: D417 [Spaniards (?)], 1938-05 (Box 3, Folder 11-1121)
  - Photo Unit #: D422 [Officers addressing the troops], 1938-05 (Box 3, Folder 11-1122)
  - Photo Unit #: D424 15th International Brigade [meeting?], 1938-05 (Box 6, Folder 11-1760)
    (Moscow Number: 5/177/44)
  - Photo Unit #: D427 [Officers addressing the troops], 1938-05 (Box 3, Folder 11-1123)
  - Photo Unit #: D429 [Soldiers marching], 1938-05 (Box 3, Folder 11-1124)
  - Photo Unit #: D434 [At attention, staff meeting (?)], 1938-05 (Box 3, Folder 11-1125)
  - Photo Unit #: D438 15th International Brigade on watch, [marching on road with flag], 1938-05 (Box 6, Folder 11-1761)
    (Moscow Number: 5/180/1)
  - Photo Unit #: D439 [Soldiers, marching], 1938-05 (Box 3, Folder 11-1126)
  - Photo Unit #: D441 [Officers addressing the troops], 1938-05 (Box 3, Folder 11-1127)
  - Photo Unit #: D442 [Officers addressing the troops], 1938-05 (Box 3, Folder 11-1128)
  - Photo Unit #: D443 [Soldiers, marching], 1938-05 (Box 3, Folder 11-1129)
  - Photo Unit #: D445 [At attention, staff meeting (?)], 1938-06 (Box 3, Folder 11-1130)
  - Photo Unit #: D446 [Soldiers, marching], 1938-05 (Box 3, Folder 11-1131)
  - Photo Unit #: D447 [At attention, staff meeting (?)], 1938-05 (Box 3, Folder 11-1132)
  - Photo Unit #: D449 Square in Alcorisa, 1938-01 (Box 3, Folder 11-1133)
  - Photo Unit #: D451 Fountain in Alcorisa, 1938-01 (Box 3, Folder 11-0868)
  - Photo Unit #: D452 Fountain in Alcorisa, 1938-01 (Box 3, Folder 11-0869)
  - Photo Unit #: D454 Showers, Ebro Front, 1938-04 (Box 8, Folder 11-1386)
  - Photo Unit #: D459 Ambulance from Teachers Union and American Student Union, Murray Nemeroff driving, 1938-05 (Box 3, Folder 11-0870)
  - Photo Unit #: D460 Ambulance from Teachers Union and American Student Union, Murray Nemeroff driving, 1938-05 (Box 3, Folder 11-0871)
  - Photo Unit #: D462 Campesinos at dance in Valls, 1938-05 (Box 3, Folder 11-1134)
  - Photo Unit #: D469 Practicing infiltration: Cabos School, 1938-05 (Box 3, Folder 11-1135)
  - Photo Unit #: D472 15th International Brigade School for Cabos, 1938-05 (Box 3, Folder 11-1136)
  - Photo Unit #: D475 Hospital at Valls, 1938-05 (Box 3, Folder 11-1137)
  - Photo Unit #: D485 British Battalion listening to John Gollan [not visible], Ulldemolins, 1938-01 (Box 8, Folder 11-1387)
  - Photo Unit #: D486 British Battalion listening to John Gollan, Ulldemolins, 1938-05 (Box 3, Folder 11-1138)
  - Photo Unit #: D495 Funeral of Lieutenant William Digges, Mollerusa, 1938-05 (Box 3, Folder 11-1139)
  - Photo Unit #: D496 Funeral of Lieutenant William Digges, Mollerusa [soldiers carrying coffin], 1938-01 (Box 8, Folder 11-1388)
  - Photo Unit #: D497 Funeral of Lieutenant William Digges, Mollerusa, 1938-05 (Box 3, Folder 11-1140)
  - Photo Unit #: D498 Funeral of Lieutenant William Digges, Mollerusa, 1938-05 (Box 3, Folder 11-1141)
  - Photo Unit #: D499 Funeral of Lieutenant William Digges, Mollerusa [soldiers at graveside], 1938-05 (Box 8, Folder 11-1389)
  - Photo Unit #: D506 Activist Congress, Marca, 1938-06 (Box 3, Folder 11-1142)
  - Photo Unit #: D509 Some delegates, Activist Congress, Marca, 1938-06 (Box 3, Folder 11-1143)
  - Photo Unit #: D511 Louis Bortz (Bradely) [?] mail censor, Barcelona, 1938-05 (Box 3, Folder 11-1144)
  - Photo Unit #: D513 Fascists taken prisoner (150) Belchite, 1939-09 (Box 3, Folder 11-1145)
  - Photo Unit #: D514 Fascists taken prisoner (150) Belchite, 1939-09 (Box 3, Folder 11-1146)
  - Photo Unit #: D515 Fascists taken prisoner (150) Belchite, 1939-09 (Box 3, Folder 11-1147)
  - Photo Unit #: D516 Fascists taken prisoner (150) Belchite, 1939-09 (Box 3, Folder 11-1148)
  - Photo Unit #: D518 Refugees from Belchite, 1939-09 (Box 3, Folder 11-1149)
    (Moscow Number: 5/191/102)
  - Photo Unit #: D523 15th International Brigade on train ride, Valencia, 1937-12 (Box 3, Folder 11-1150)
  - Photo Unit #: D525 Cabo School, Ebro Front, 1938-05 (Box 3, Folder 11-1151)
  - Photo Unit #: D527 Fiesta, MacKenzie-Papineau and civilians at Tivisa, Edward Cecil Smith, David Doran, Frank Rogers, 1938-05-13 (Box 8, Folder 11-1390)
  - Photo Unit #: D545 School for Commissars, Ebro Front, 1938-05 (Box 3, Folder 11-1152)
  - Photo Unit #: D546 MacKenzie-Papineau, Hijar, 1938-05 (Box 8, Folder 11-1391)
  - Photo Unit #: D550 Swim and change of clothes for 15th International Brigade, 1938-05 (Box 8, Folder 11-1392)
    (Moscow Number: 5/191/93)
  - Photo Unit #: D556 Football game, 13th and 15th International Brigades, Tarraga, 1938-05 (Box 3, Folder 11-1153)
    (Moscow Number: 5/192/1)
  - Photo Unit #: D558 Football game, 13th and 15th International Brigades, Tarraga, 1938-05 (Box 3, Folder 11-1154)
  - Photo Unit #: D562 British Battalion machine-gun company, Tarraga, 1938-05 (Box 6, Folder 11-1816)
    (Moscow Number: 5/185/16)
  - Photo Unit #: D565 Soldiers at Activists Congress, Marca, 1938-06 (Box 3, Folder 11-1155)
  - Photo Unit #: D569 Sanidad [Health], lunch time, Marca, 1938-06 (Box 3, Folder 11-1156)
  - Photo Unit #: D571 Trade Union Delegation at MacKenzie-Papineau, in the vineyards, 1938-06 (Box 8, Folder 11-1393)
  - Photo Unit #: D577 Recruit group building fortifications, Marca [copy negative; transferred from the Victor Berch Papers, ALBA 080], 1938-06 (Box 6, Folder 11-1897)
  - Photo Unit #: D578 Lincoln-Washington boys with peasants tending vines, Marca, 1938-06 (Box 8, Folder 11-1394)
  - Photo Unit #: D579 MacKenzie-Papineau group marching to vineyards, 1938-06 (Box 3, Folder 11-1157)
  - Photo Unit #: D582 MacKenzie-Papineau group working in vineyards, Marca, 1938-06 (Box 3, Folder 11-1198)
  - Photo Unit #: D585 Joseph Brandt of Lincoln-Washington Battalion reading news, 1938-06 (Box 3, Folder 11-0872)
  - Photo Unit #: D587 Hospital, wounded soldier reading in bed, undated (Box 8, Folder 11-1395)
  - Photo Unit #: D599 Auto Park, Alcover, 1939-08 (Box 8, Folder 11-1396)
  - Photo Unit #: D600 Volunteer for Liberty, Alcover, 1939-08 (Box 3, Folder 11-1158)
- Series E: Miscellaneous, 1938-01-1939-09
  Series IIE: Miscellaneous, January 1938 - September 1938. Many of the 761 images in this series capture the final battles of the International Brigades. The most arresting shots are those taken at the crossing of the Ebro in July 1938. In an article that appeared in the Volunteer for Liberty in September 1938, Randall described the Photo Unit's activities and the photographic record they created during the Ebro Offensive:
  "In the period of reorganization and training that preceded our crossing of the Ebro, we were busy snapping pictures of training schools, delegations, fiestas, activities, meetings, classes, congresses, etc. Then the moment came when we prepared to attack. Ben Katine took a fine set of pictures of our comrades crossing the river in boats and rafts of the building of the first footbridge and the first groups of our soldiers to walk across it to the west bank of the Ebro, ours once more. We went ahead with our troops as we advanced, and later made pictures of the ruins of towns bombed by the Fascist planes."
  This series also includes pictures of peasants working in the fields of Marca; the presentation of a flag by Juventud Socialista Unificada (Unified Socialist Youth of the Spanish Communist Party); and the evacuation of wounded in Gandesa.
  - Photo Unit #: E0001 Lincoln Brigade troops marching to North Pole, Teruel Sector [snowy landscape with distant figures], 1938-01 (Box 8, Folder 11-1397)
  - Photo Unit #: E0002 Company 2, Lincoln-Washington Battalion trench at North Pole, Teruel Sector, 1938-01 (Box 8, Folder 11-1398)
  - Photo Unit #: E0003 Lincoln-Washington Battalion trench at North Pole, Teruel Sector, 1938-01 (Box 8, Folder 11-1399)
  - Photo Unit #: E0005 Officers of 15th International Brigade and others at North Pole, Teruel Sector, 1938-01 (Box 8, Folder 11-1400)
  - Photo Unit #: E0006 Alvin Cohen, action scene, Company 1, Lincoln-Washington Battalion North Pole, Teruel Sector, 1938-01 (Box 8, Folder 11-1401)
  - Photo Unit #: E0007 Action Scene, Company 2, Lincoln-Washington, North Pole, Teruel Sector, 1938-01 (Box 1, Folder 11-0064)
  - Photo Unit #: E0008 Spain 1938, scene in Terrega, 1938-05 (Box 8, Folder 11-1402)
  - Photo Unit #: E0011 Lincoln-Washington Battalion trench at North Pole, Teruel Sector, 1938-01 (Box 8, Folder 11-1403)
  - Photo Unit #: E0012 Lincoln-Washington Battalion trench at North Pole, Teruel Sector, 1938-01 (Box 8, Folder 11-1404)
  - Photo Unit #: E0013 Lincoln-Washington Battalion trench at North Pole, Teruel Sector, 1938-01 (Box 8, Folder 11-1405)
  - Photo Unit #: E0014 Lincoln-Washington Battalion trench at North Pole, Teruel Sector, 1938-01 (Box 8, Folder 11-1406)
  - Photo Unit #: E0015 Lincoln-Washington Battalion trench at North Pole, Teruel Sector, 1938-01 (Box 8, Folder 11-1407)
  - Photo Unit #: E0016 Lincoln-Washington Battalion trench at North Pole, Teruel Sector, 1938-01 (Box 1, Folder 11-0065)
  - Photo Unit #: E0017 Lincoln-Washington digging Battalion trench at North Pole, Teruel Sector, 1938-01 (Box 9, Folder 11-1408)
  - Photo Unit #: E0019 Lincoln-Washington Battalion trench at North Pole, Teruel Sector, 1938-01 (Box 9, Folder 11-1409)
  - Photo Unit #: E0020 Lincoln-Washington Battalion marching to Teruel Sector, 1938-01 (Box 1, Folder 11-0066)
  - Photo Unit #: E0022 Lincoln-Washington Battalion trench at North Pole, Teruel Sector, 1938-01 (Box 9, Folder 11-1410)
  - Photo Unit #: E0023 Captain Leonard Lamb and Captain Milton Wolff of Lincoln-Washington Battalion at North Pole, 1938-01 (Box 9, Folder 11-1411)
  - Photo Unit #: E0024 Action Scene, Company 1, Lincoln-Washington Battalion at North Pole, Teruel, 1938-01 (Box 9, Folder 11-1412)
  - Photo Unit #: E0025 Action Scene, Company 1, Lincoln-Washington Battalion at North Pole, Teruel, 1938-01 (Box 9, Folder 11-1413)
  - Photo Unit #: E0026 Machine-Gun Company 1, Lincoln-Washington Battalion at North Pole, Teruel, 1938-01 (Box 9, Folder 11-1414)